<persona id="peepshow_mark" displayName="(Peep Show) Mark Corrigan">
    <quote type="other">Sure, an orgy sounds great, but you're basically just multiplying the number of people you're not going to be able to look in the eye afterwards.</quote>
    <quote type="other">Socks before or after trousers, but never socks before pants, that's the rule. Makes a man look scary, like a chicken.</quote>
    <quote type="failure">Jeremy, there are many things I would do to help you, but digging a hole in the wintry earth with my bear hands so that you can bury the corpse of a dog you've killed is not one of them.</quote>
    <quote type="failure">Okay, here we go, wedding day. I am heading for a wedding. How do I feel? Empty, check. Scared, check. Alone, check. Just another ordinary day.</quote>
    <quote type="other">I want to call again, but when I leave long messages, I have this nagging sense that I'll end up hearing them played back to me in a court of law.</quote>
    <quote type="success">I do sort of like it when he's rude to me. Hopefully that's more of a psychological defect, not a weird sexual thing.</quote>
    <quote type="failure">Maybe this is what it'll be like after the apocalypse, wandering around depressed, shooting children for fun.</quote>
    <quote type="failure">It's been like eating a vast portion of chips: Very comfortable, but there's this lurking sense that you're killing yourself.</quote>
    <quote type="other">Ugh, that was horrible. Now he probably thinks I'm embarrassed about the size of my penis. When in fact I'm not, I'm much more concerned about my misshapen scrotum.</quote>
    <quote type="success">Sophie's the one. Toni's Russia; vast, mysterious, unconquerable. Sophie's Poland; manageable, won't put up too much of a fight.</quote>
    <quote type="success">Look at me, friends with a big black businessman like it's the most natural thing in the world. If he got accused of a crime he hadn't committed I could come to his aid.</quote>
    <quote type="success">Brown for first course, white for pudding. Brown's savoury, white's the treat. Course I'm the one who's laughing because I actually love brown toast.</quote>
    <quote type="other">The truth is... The truth is, I suppose, I like you. That's why I said the song. I like you. Is that such a crime? Should I be hounded to the ends of the Earth just for liking you? I like you and if you can't handle it, you can just... you know, fuck off.</quote>
    <quote type="other">Is this a bit like stalking? Stalking's a very loaded term, I prefer to think of it as extreme liking.</quote>
    <quote type="other">There's probably much less to worry about with gay sex. I mean, you know where you are with a cock.</quote>
    <quote type="failure">No, Soph. We've got to push on, push on to Moscow.</quote>
    <quote type="success">This is a mega-funeral. It was a mega-interview. Hugh was the only real rival, but look what's happened to Gerrard. This is what I do to rivals, I put my rivals in the ground.</quote>
    <quote type="failure">Yeah, you won't be so cocky, Jeff, when I come into the office with a Kalashnikov and 200 rounds of ammunition.</quote>
    <quote type="other">Jeremy, do you think we could take a brief time-out from the masturbate-athon that is your life to go to my son's Christening?</quote>
    <quote type="success">I've won! It's like I'm Napoleon invading Moscow and the Tsar's fucked off to Ibiza! I've conquered the whole of Russia! I've only gone and won!</quote>
</persona>